<Publish>
  <ModId Value="90641" />
  <DisplayName Value="Hall of Fame" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Share screenshots with the community and get inspiration in return" />
  <LongDescription># Hall of Fame for Cities: Skylines II

**Share screenshots and admire other creators’ work, all in-game!**

## What does it do?

If you’re in one of those situations, all you need is the mod!

- You hate that you spend so much time on a city, but no one sees it, or at best you post it on
  Reddit, and it still gets forgotten after a few days.
- You want to show off your detailing or city-planning skills.
- You want some inspiration when you fire up the game.
- You’re too lazy to open Reddit and three Discord servers to see some cool cities.
- Oh, and last but not least: the mod allows you to take **4K screenshots**, even when playing at a
  lower resolution, and **makes better screenshot renders than the Vanilla tool**!

This mod allows players to take and upload 4K screenshots of their city and share them with the
community.

Images can then be viewed and liked by other players as a background image in the main menu, and
hopefully soon enough, on the web!

Hall of Fame also makes sure no city falls into oblivion by displaying each uploaded image as often
as possible!

The likes and trending screenshots mechanisms still allow the best creators to shine, but everyone
is welcome, there is no downvote and no moderation based on skill.

## Rules

### Should I be a pro-detailer to share my screenshots?

**Every** player is welcome to share their creations!
The content is not selected or moderated based on quality or complexity.

Don’t be shy, let us remember your city — if you wanna share it, we wanna see it!

### Linking social media platforms

Next to your username when displaying one of your pictures, Hall of Fame can display buttons leading
to your other social media accounts.

The following platforms are supported: Paradox Mods, YouTube, Twitch and Discord (invite link),
others can be added on demand if the platform is popular enough.

Your channel/account must contain a fair amount of C:S 2 content to be eligible, of course.

To link your social media to your HoF creator account, you need to contact me (via any medium, best
is Discord, you can also use halloffame at mtq.io) and provide me with your username and links.

### Post-processing and other mods

Yes! — you can use any assets and mods you want. This includes post-processing mods that change
camera settings, add effects, etc., as well as custom content, textures, LUTs, etc.

One of such mods is Lumina, check it out! https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/94394/Windows

The only thing to keep in mind is that the screenshot should still showcase something you can
actually do in the game, including heavily modded, but without external tools.
So, no tampering of the image with other software is allowed; this is not the spirit.

### Inappropriate content

Inappropriate, offensive, provoking, off-topic content will be removed, and your account will be
permanently prohibited from using the service, without warning.

A report button is available in the main menu to report inappropriate content.
It will be immediately unlisted and reviewed by a human.

## Participate in the project

### Get support, report bugs, discuss

You can join the Cities: Skylines Modding Discord server and join us in the dedicated thread
**pdxm-mods-published › Hall of Fame**.

Bug reports with useful reproduction steps and logs are also very welcome on GitHub!

For other requests or if you do not have a Discord account, you can reach me at
**halloffame at mtq.io**.

### Feedback and Feature requests

We have a feedback and feature requests board here where you can suggest and vote on features you’d
like to see in the mod: https://feedback.halloffame.cs2.mtq.io

It takes a minute to sign up, but your feedback would be very appreciated!

### Translations

The mod is translated by the community on Crowdin: https://crowdin.com/project/halloffame-cs2

New languages can be added on request, and corrections are very welcome!

### Donating

Hall of Fame has monthly running costs: hosting the server and your images is not free!

Donations are very welcome and will help keep the service running.

## Special Thanks

- **The Cities: Skylines Modding Discord community** in general for their help and kind support.
- **Chamëleon (@chameleon_tbn)** for creating some UI icons for the mod and algernon for exposing
  them in the Unified Icon Library.
- **Bad Peanut** for the Hearth Chirper icon.
- **b00tyaddict, CloverPie, Danil.V.L, Hendrix, Jason_Stephen, Jojodaisuke, Konsi, obelix, Prophedt,
  TheBusStop, ThemisC2, Tigon Ologdring**, valuable community members who, in one way or the other,
  provided a lot of help, feedback, support and enthusiasm.
- **Translators:**
  baka-gourd (Chinese Simplified),
  elGendo87 (Spanish),
  Finn (Dutch),
  Fuchs23 (German),
  Hendrix_ (German)
  karmel68 (Polish),
  Konsi (German),
  RilkeXS (Chinese Simplified),
  ThemisC2 (Italian),
  Tiago Correia (Portuguese),
  toverux (French),
  y1ito4ka (Russian).
- **ThemisC2** for his hum, *relentless* support to help me finally finish a personal project.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Preview1.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot2.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot3.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot4.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot5.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot6.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot7.png" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/hall-of-fame.1704820/" />
  <ModVersion Value="2026.0.0" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
  <ChangeLog>**The screenshot metadata update!**

Restructured upload popup for attaching information about your screenshots:
- Choose whether to share your photo mode settings,
- Choose whether to share your mods playset,
- Select a showcased asset or map, to demo how you used a Paradox Mods asset and make a little publicity for it, as an asset author or satisfied user!
- Four thousand characters of Markdown description! Write the story of your city, explain detailing techniques you’ve used, a poem, anything.

For this update, only the showcased asset/map will be shown in the Hall of Fame’s main menu carousel. \
The description or photo mode settings and playset are not yet shown in the UI, but this will be implemented soon. \
Allowing you to set them right now allows you to start adding more context to your screenshots.

In a second time, a mass editor will also allow you to edit your previous screenshots to add these fields if you wish.</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/toverux/HallOfFame" />
  <ExternalLink Type="crowdin" Url="https://crowdin.com/project/halloffame-cs2" />
  <ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://paypal.me/MorganTouverey" />
  <ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/toverux" />
</Publish>