<Publish>
  <ModId Value="90641" />
  <DisplayName Value="Hall of Fame" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Share screenshots with the community and get inspiration in return" />
  <LongDescription># Hall of Fame for Cities: Skylines II

## What does it do?

If you’re in one of those situations, all you need is the mod!
- You hate that you spend so much time on a city, but no one sees it, or at best
  you post it on Reddit, and it still gets forgotten after a few days.
- You want to show off your detailing or city-planning skills.
- You want some inspiration when you fire up the game.
- You’re too lazy to open Reddit and three Discord servers to see some cool
  cities.
- Oh, and last but not least: the mod allows you to take **4K screenshots**,
  even when playing at a lower resolution, and **makes better screenshot
  renders than the Vanilla tool**!

This mod allows players to take and upload 4K screenshots of their city, and
share them with the community. Images can then be viewed by other players as a
background image in the main menu, with information about the creator, the city
name, and controls to refresh the image, like/favorite or hide the menu UI to
better see the image, to name a few features.

Hall of Fame then makes sure that no city falls into oblivion, by displaying
each uploaded images as often as possible.

The likes and trending screenshots mechanisms still allows the best creators to
shine, but everyone is welcome, there is no downvote and no moderation based on
skill.

## Features

- Supersampling all screenshots you make to **4K** resolution even if you play
  at a lower resolution, and makes better renders than the game’s native
  screenshot tool.
- Have pictures displayed in the main menu, with various information about the
  city, the author, etc.
- Give a like to the pictures you appreciate and see popular pictures.
- Toggle menu UI visibility to admire the pictures (like a slideshow).
- Fine-tune how the algorithm chooses screenshots that are presented to you
  (recent screenshots, most liked, ancient and forgotten, etc.).
- Make screenshots and upload them via a dedicated interface, all in-game.
- Choose between Full HD and 4K resolution for pictures shown in the main menu.

**Much more to come!** See our feedback and feature requests board to follow the
development and suggest/upvote features:
https://feedback.halloffame.cs2.mtq.io

## Rules

### Should I be a pro detailer to share my screenshots?

**Every** player is welcome to share their creations!
The content is not selected or moderated based on quality or complexity.

Don’t be shy, let us remember your city — if you wanna share it, we wanna see
it!

### Post-processing and other mods

Yes! — you can use any assets and mods you want. This includes post-processing
mods that change camera settings, add effects, etc., as well a custom content,
textures, LUTs, etc.

One of such mods is Lumina, check it out!
https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/94394/Windows

The only thing to keep in mind is that the screenshot should still showcase
something you can actually do in the game, including heavily modded, but without
external tools.
So, no tampering of the image with other software is allowed, this is not the
spirit.

### Inappropriate content

Inappropriate, offensive, provoking, off-topic content will be removed and your
account will be permanently prohibited from using the service, without warning.

A report button is available in the main menu to report inappropriate content.
It will be immediately unlisted and reviewed by a human.

## Participate in the project

### Get support, report bugs, discuss

You can join the Cities: Skylines Modding Discord server and join us in the
dedicated thread **pdxm-mods-published › Hall of Fame**.

Bug reports with useful reproduction steps and/or logs are also very welcome on
GitHub!

### Feedback and Feature requests

We have a feedback and feature requests board here where you can suggest and
vote on features you’d like to see in the mod:
https://feedback.halloffame.cs2.mtq.io

It takes a minute to sign up, but your feedback would be very appreciated!

### Translations

The mod is translated by the community on Crowdin:
https://crowdin.com/project/halloffame-cs2

New languages can be added on request and corrections are very welcome!

### Donating

Hall of Fame has low, but nonetheless existing, running costs: hosting the
server and your images is not free.

Donations are very welcome and will help keep the service running.

## Special Thanks

- **The Cities: Skylines Modding Discord community** in general for their help
  and kind support.
- **Chamëleon (@chameleon_tbn)** for creating some UI icons for the mod.
- **Bad Peanut** for the Hearth Chirper icon.
- **b00tyaddict, CloverPie, Danil.V.L, Hendrix, Jason_Stephen, Jojodaisuke,
  Konsi, obelix, Prophedt, TheBusStop, ThemisC2, Tigon Ologdring**, valuable
  community members who, in one way or the other, provided a lot of help,
  feedback, support and enthusiasm.
- **Translators:**
  baka-gourd (Chinese Simplified),
  elGendo87 (Spanish),
  Finn (Dutch),
  Fuchs23 (German),
  karmel68 (Polish),
  Konsi (German),
  RilkeXS (Chinese Simplified),
  ThemisC2 (Italian),
  Tiago Correia (Portuguese),
  toverux (French),
  y1ito4ka (Russian).
- **ThemisC2** for his hum, *relentless* support to help me finally finish a
  personal project.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot1.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot2.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot3.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot4.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot5.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot6.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot7.png" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/hall-of-fame.1704820/" />
  <ModVersion Value="1.7.1" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
  <Dependency Id="74417" DisplayName="Unified Icon Library" />
  <Dependency Id="75426" DisplayName="I18n EveryWhere" />
  <ChangeLog>Localization update for many languages.</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/toverux/HallOfFame" />
  <ExternalLink Type="crowdin" Url="https://crowdin.com/project/halloffame-cs2" />
  <ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://paypal.me/MorganTouverey" />
  <ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/toverux" />
</Publish>